typing-speed.net 2012-12-23

# ScreeneNetwork.com - Privacy Policy

|  **SCREENENETWORK - PRIVACY POLICY** This privacy policy applies to most of our websites. We respect the privacy of our visitors and surfers. We do not sell, barter or exchange email addresses you give us when sending a greeting unless a visitor has given us explicit permission to do so. We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, and may be disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website. 

We reserve the right to provide information if we think - correctly or incorrectly and reasonably or unreasonably - that our greetings, ecards, quiz cards, wishafriend greetings and comments, screensavers and/or wallpapers are being used in violation of our terms of use, including, but not limited to, being used in any illegal, harmful, threatening or anti-social activity. 

We try to protect your privacy, but please understand that any use of the Internet or of email creates the possibility that someone could access the data transmitted. There is always some risk on the web that personal information might be accessed and privacy cannot be guaranteed. 

**Advertisers, Affiliates and Others:**   
Before providing information to any party other than screenenetwork.com, you should check their privacy policy, as they are third parties. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices utilized by any other sites, linked by us.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

From time to time, we may use customer information, if collected, for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

Facebook connect is used by us on some of our websites to connect our surfers to Facebook.com. The operation of this service is obviously dependent on Facebook. Please note that whatever you share on Facebook is done explicitly by you on your own will. Only you yourself can control what you share on your Facebook. You need to see your privacy settings in your Facebook account. 

We can be reached on e-mail. For any queries, contact us. 

|
